Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Creative Services, 1964-2007; (80 boxes)
  - Subseries 2: Chronological, 1981-2007
    - 2001, August 31-October 30, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      Awards ceremony; Admissions open house; School of Management, DLAMP course; Fall for the Book; Nathan the wise rehearsal; employee of the month Jason Liddell; School of Management scholarship; School of Management advisory board; SBA
    - 2001, November 1-December 10, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      Mathy House; Legacy society; GMU trademark; Anthony Maiello
    - 2002, 2002-April 2, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 7)
      Twins biography admissions shoot; Richard Klimoski (School of Management); dance; Bernstein's Mass; Homecoming; Awards ceremony; Outstanding awards; Bateson retirement; EMBA group photo; dance reception
      contact sheets, black and white photographs
    - 2002, April 25-June 24, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      Mason Day; Olympic team visit; students on campus (snow); dance
    - 2002, August 30-November 22, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      Ceremony awards; School of Management; check presentation
    - 2003, April 13-October 31, 2003 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      Students on campus (cherry blossoms); Orientation leaders; Supervisor series; graduation; dance; Concert Wind Symphony; New York City art bus
    - 2004, January 16-May 1, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      Dance; Capital goal achievement announcement; EMBA group; Homecoming block party; Mason Day; Robotics IT&E; Admissions D.C., Lincoln memorial (040501)
    - 2004, May 15-July 2004 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      Graduation (color slides); Johnson Center dining (CDs)
      contact sheets, negatives, slides, CD
    - 2005, March 2-May 21, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      Admissions shots, student leaders; commencement
      slides, CD
    - 2005, October 14, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      Candlight vigil
      slides, negatives
    - 2007, June 28-December, 2007 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      Employee of the month; President and Mrs. Alan Merten; Miscellaneous Christmas (negatives)
  - Subseries 3: Publications, 1987-2000
    This series is arranged alphabetically. Formats include black and white photographs, color photographs, slides, negatives, and contact sheets with their corresponding brochures, reports, posters, or newsletters.
    - Admissions - "University scholar facts", and "After admissions what to expect", circa 1990s (Box 114, Folder 7)
      black and white photographs, brochures
    - Alumni Association annual report and brochure, 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      black and white photographs, report, brochure
    - Annual Fund brochure, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Benefactor newsletter, November 1997-October 1998 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      newsletters, slides
    - Camp Mason: University Day Camp, 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      brocures, black and white photographs
    - Children related brochures, 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      black and white photographs, pamphlets
    - Computational Sciences and Informatics (CSI), 1999 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      slides, brochure
    - Constraint programming poster, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Department of Instructional Improvement and Instructional Technologies (DOIIT), 1998 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      brochure, photocopy
    - Education PhD program brochure, circa 1990s (Box 114, Folder 16)
      brochure, black and white photographs
    - Entrepeneurship Center brochure, circa 1990s (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Facilities brochure, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Faculty bibliography, undated (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Factsheets for Arts & Sciences, Information Technology and Engineering, circa 1990s (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Forum Futures magazine, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Gazette, August 1987 (?) (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Gazette, November 24, 1997-February 25, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      black and white photographs and slides with corresponding Gazette issues
    - Gazette, March 1998-March 1999 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      black and white photographs with corresponding Gazette issues
    - Gazette, April 1999-March 2000 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      black and white photographs, color photograph, slide with corresponding Gazette issues
    - Gazette, May 2000 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Health, fitness, and recreation resources (HRFF), 2000 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Honors program, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      black and white photographs, poster, brochures and mock ups
    - Housing brochure, circa 1990s (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Inauguration of President Alan Merten, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      black and white photographs, color photographs, slides, program
    - Information technology, circa 1998 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      color contact sheets, color negatives, brochures
    - The Institute for Biosciences, Bioinformatics, and Biotechnology (IB3), 1998 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      black and white photograph, slides, brochures
    - The Institute of the Arts, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 11)
      black and white photographs, slides, brochures (visual art, theatre, dance)
    - Internal audit and management services brochures, circa 1990s (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Law School prospectus, Fall 1996, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      black and white photographs, color photographs, slides, brochures
    - Learning communities and libraries, 1990s (Box 116, Folder 1)
      slides, brochures
    - Mason Spirit magazine, Spring 1998-Winter 1999 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      black and white photographs with corresponding Mason Spirit issues
    - Mason summer Saturday, August 1998 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Master of Arts in International Transactions (MAIT), circa 1990s (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Music, multiple publications, circa 1990s (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - New Century College, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      slides
    - Open House brochures, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Preview invites, "put your degree to work", 1998 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      black and white photograph, brochure
    - Prospectus, 1996-1998 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      color photographs, negatives, slides, brochures
    - Prospectus, 1998-1999 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      color photographs, slides, prospectus
    - Prospectus, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      color photographs, slides, negatives
    - Prospectus for Law School, 1999-2000 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      black and white photographs, prospectus
    - Psychology, 1996-1998 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      black and white photographs, slides
    - Schedule of classes, Summer 1998-Summer 1999 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      black and white photographs, schedules
    - Schedule of classes, Summer 2000 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      slides, schedule
    - Social work brochure, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      black and white photographs, brochure
    - Student handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      black and white photographs, handbooks
    - Student handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Student handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Summer Arts Academy, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Summer Arts Academy, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Summer Arts Academy, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - The Institute for Public Policy (TIPP), 1998 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      color photograph, slides, brochure
    - Train to Technology (TTT) program, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      black and white photographs, pamphlet
    - University Catalog, 1997-1999 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - University Scholars program, circa 1990s (Box 118, Folder 1)
      slide, application packets
    - Washington Post - athletics program, April 20, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - World Congress brochure, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      slide, brochure
  - Subseries 4: Photo albums, 1988-2000
    Subseries four consists of fourteen disassembled photo albums. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject. Many of these photographs also have specific order numbers and are arranged numerically as well.
    - Art and performing arts classes, 1991-1998 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Buildings on campus except for the Johnson Center, 1990-1999 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Buildings on campus - Johnson Center, 1995-1999 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Classrooms, science labs, 1989-1998 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Computers, 1993-1998 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Events, 1991-1998 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Graduation, 1995-1998 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Housing, admissions, registration, information, bookstore, 1991-1997 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Mason community, sports, 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Nursing, 1996, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Police, sports, Cablecast facilities (TV), 1992-1997 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Students at Fenwick Library and Johnson Center, 1993-1998 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Student groups, 1988-1998 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Students - individually and in groups, Johnson Center Cinema, dining, dance class (color), 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 17)